Finding Aid for Alexander G. Ruthven Papers
Bentley Historical Library
- President's Office, 1929-1952
  - Correspondence Files, 1929-1951
    - 1931-1932
      - Lf-Lz (Box 5)
        (5-20)
      - Ma (Box 5)
        (5-21)
      - Mb-Me (Box 5)
        (5-22)
      - Memberships (Ruthven) (Box 5)
        (5-23)
      - Mf-Mz (Box 5)
        (5-24)
      - Michigan League (Box 5)
        (5-25)
      - Murfin, James O. (Box 5)
        (5-26)
      - N (Box 6)
        (6-1)
      - O (Box 6)
        (6-2)
      - Pa-Ph (Box 6)
        (6-3)
      - Pearce, Webster R. (Box 6)
        (6-4)
      - Pi-Pz (Box 6)
        (6-5)
      - Q (Box 6)
        (6-6)
      - Ra-Ri (Box 6)
        (6-7)
      - Rj-Rz (Box 6)
        (6-8)
      - R.O.T.C. (Box 6)
        (6-9)
      - Sa-Sc (Box 6)
        (6-10)
      - Sd-Sh (Box 6)
        (6-11)
      - Si-Sm (Box 6)
        (6-12)
      - Smith, Ira M (Box 6)
        (6-13)
      - Smith, Richard R. (Box 6)
        (6-14)
      - Smith, Shirley W. (Box 6)
        (6-15)
      - Sm-Sz (Box 6)
        (6-16)
      - Stone, Ralph (Box 6)
        (6-17)
      - T (Box 6)
        (6-18)
      - U-V (Box 6)
        (6-19)
      - Wa (Box 6)
        (6-20)
      - Wb-Wh (Box 6)
        (6-21)
      - Wi-Wz (Box 6)
        (6-22)
      - X-Z (Box 6)
        (6-23)
    - 1932-1933
      - Aa-Am (Box 6)
        (6-24)
      - Alumni Association (Box 6)
        (6-25)
      - American (Box 6)
        (6-26)
      - An-Az (Box 6)
        (6-27)
      - Associations (Box 6)
        (6-28)
      - Ba (Box 7)
        (7-1)
      - Bb-Bi (Box 7)
        (7-2)
      - Bishop, William W. (Box 7)
        (7-3)
      - Bj-Bo (Box 7)
        (7-4)
      - Board in Control of Athletics (Box 7)
        (7-5)
      - Bp-Bz (Box 7)
        (7-6)
      - Ca-Ce (Box 7)
        (7-7)
      - Cd-Cl (Box 7)
        (7-8)
      - Chase, Fred (Box 7)
        (7-9)
      - Cm-Co (Box 7)
        (7-10)
      - Clements Library (Box 7)
        (7-11)
      - Cp-Cz (Box 7)
        (7-12)
      - Da-Do (Box 7)
        (7-13)
      - Dana, Samuel T. (Box 7)
        (7-14)
      - Dormitories (Box 7)
        (7-15)
      - Dp-Dz (Box 7)
        (7-16)
      - Ea-Ez (Box 7)
        (7-17)
      - Earhart, Harry B. (Box 7)
        (7-18)
      - Fa-Fh (Box 7)
        (7-19)
      - Fi-Fq (Box 7)
        (7-20)
      - Fr-Fz (Box 7)
        (7-21)
      - Ga-Go (Box 7)
        (7-22)
      - Gp-Gz (Box 7)
        (7-23)
      - Griffin, Dean C.E. (Box 7)
        (7-24)
      - Ha-Hd (Box 7)
        (7-25)
      - He-Ho (Box 7)
        (7-26)
      - Hillel Foundation (Box 7)
        (7-27)
      - Hp-Hz (Box 7)
        (7-28)
      - Hubbard, Lucius L. (Box 7)
        (7-29)
      - I (Box 7)
        (7-30)
      - Ives Memorial Camp (Box 7)
        (7-31)
      - J (Box 7)
        (7-32)
      - Ka-Kh (Box 7)
        (7-33)
      - Ki-Kz (Box 7)
        (7-34)
      - La-Lh (Box 8)
        (8-1)
      - Li-Lz (Box 8)
        (8-2)
      - Ma (Box 8)
        (8-3)
      - Mb-Mc (Box 8)
        (8-4)
      - Md-Mh (Box 8)
        (8-5)
      - Memberships (Ruthven) (Box 8)
        (8-6)
      - Mi-Mz (Box 8)
        (8-7)
      - Moore, Senator Andrew L. (Box 8)
        (8-8)
      - Murfin, James O. (Box 8)
        (8-9)
      - Na-Nz (Box 8)
        (8-10)
      - North Central Association (Box 8)
        (8-11)
      - O (Box 8)
        (8-12)
      - Pa-Pe (Box 8)
        (8-13)
      - Pearce, Webster H. (Box 8)
        (8-14)
      - Pf-Pz (Box 8)
        (8-15)
      - Q (Box 8)
        (8-16)
      - Ra-Ri (Box 8)
        (8-17)
      - Religious Education (Box 8)
        (8-18)
      - R.O.T.C. (Box 8)
        (8-19)
      - Rj-Rz (Box 8)
        (8-20)
      - Sa-Sc (Box 8)
        (8-21)
      - Scholarships (Religion) (Box 8)
        (8-22)
      - Scott, James Brown (Box 8)
        (8-23)
      - Sd-Sh (Box 8)
        (8-24)
      - Si-Sn (Box 8)
        (8-25)
      - Smith, Shirley W. (Box 8)
        (8-26)
      - So-Sz (Box 8)
        (8-27)
      - Stone, Ralph (Box 8)
        (8-28)
      - T (Box 8)
        (8-29)
      - U-V (Box 8)
        (8-30)
      - Wa-We (Box 8)
        (8-31)
      - Wf-Wz (Box 8)
        (8-32)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 8)
        (8-33)
    - 1933-1934
      - Aa-Am (Box 9)
        (9-1)
      - Alumni Association (Box 9)
        (9-2)
      - American (Box 9)
        (9-3)
      - An-Az (Box 9)
        (9-4)
      - Associations (Box 9)
        (9-5)
      - Ba (Box 9)
        (9-6)
      - Bb-Bi (Box 9)
        (9-7)
      - Bishop, William W. (Box 9)
        (9-8)
      - Blakeman, Edward W. (Box 9)
        (9-9)
      - Bm-Br (Box 9)
        (9-10)
      - Board in Control of Athletics (Box 9)
        (9-11)
      - Bs-Bz (Box 9)
        (9-12)
      - Bruce, James D. (Box 9)
        (9-13)
      - Ca-Cd (Box 9)
        (9-14)
      - Ce-Ck (Box 9)
        (9-15)
      - Cl-Co (Box 9)
        (9-16)
      - Clements Library (Box 9)
        (9-17)
      - Cp-Cz (Box 9)
        (9-18)
      - C.W.A.; N.R.A.; P.W.A.; F.E.R.A. (Box 9)
        (9-19)
      - Da-Di (Box 9)
        (9-20)
      - Dana, Dean S.T. (Box 9)
        (9-21)
      - Dj-Dz (Box 9)
        (9-22)
      - Ea-Ez (Box 9)
        (9-23)
      - Earhart, Harry B (Box 9)
        (9-24)
      - Engineering Research (Box 9)
        (9-25)
      - Fa-Fq (Box 9)
        (9-26)
      - Fr-Fz (Box 9)
        (9-27)
      - Fresh Air Camp (Box 9)
        (9-28)
      - Ga-Go (Box 9)
        (9-29)
      - Gp-Gz (Box 9)
        (9-30)
      - Gram, L.G. (Box 9)
        (9-31)
      - Ha-Hd (Box 9)
        (9-32)
      - He-Hh (Box 9)
        (9-33)
      - Hi-Hz (Box 9)
        (9-34)
      - House of Representatives-Bills (Box 9)
        (9-35)
      - Huber, G. Carl (Box 9)
        (9-36)
      - I (Box 10)
        (10-1)
      - J (Box 10)
        (10-2)
      - Ka-Kk (Box 10)
        (10-3)
      - Kl-Kz (Box 10)
        (10-4)
      - Koelz, Walter (Box 10)
        (10-5)
      - La-Le (Box 10)
        (10-6)
      - Lawyers Club (Box 10)
        (10-7)
      - Lf-Lz (Box 10)
        (10-8)
      - Ma (Box 10)
        (10-9)
      - Mb-Md (Box 10)
        (10-10)
      - Me-Mi (Box 10)
        (10-11)
      - Memberships (Ruthven) (Box 10)
        (10-12)
      - Mj-Mz (Box 10)
        (10-13)
      - Murfin, James O. (Box 10)
        (10-14)
      - Na-Nd (Box 10)
        (10-15)
      - Ne-Nz (Box 10)
        (10-16)
      - O (Box 10)
        (10-17)
      - Pa-Pe (Box 10)
        (10-18)
      - Patents and Copyrights (Box 10)
        (10-19)
      - Pf-Pz (Box 10)
        (10-20)
      - Q (Box 10)
        (10-21)
      - Ra-Ri (Box 10)
        (10-22)
      - Rj-Rz (Box 10)
        (10-23)
      - R.O.T.C. (Box 10)
        (10-24)
      - Sa-Sh (Box 10)
        (10-25)
      - Scholarships (Box 10)
        (10-26)
      - Shields, Edmund C. (Box 10)
        (10-27)
      - Si-Sn (Box 10)
        (10-28)
      - Smith, Shirley W. (Box 10)
        (10-29)
      - So-Sz (Box 10)
        (10-30)
      - Stone, Ralph (Box 10)
        (10-31)
      - T (Box 10)
        (10-32)
      - U-V (Box 10)
        (10-33)
      - Voelker, Paul F. (Box 10)
        (10-34)
      - Wa (Box 11)
        (11-1)
      - Ward, Marcus L. (Box 11)
        (11-2)
      - Wb-Wi (Box 11)
        (11-3)
      - Wj-Wz (Box 11)
        (11-4)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 11)
        (11-5)
    - 1934-1935
      - Aa-Am (Box 11)
        (11-6)
      - Alumni Association (Box 11)
        (11-7)
      - Alumni Relations (Box 11)
        (11-8)
      - American (Box 11)
        (11-9)
      - An-Az (Box 11)
        (11-10)
      - Associations and Societies (Box 11)
        (11-11)
      - Ba (Box 11)
        (11-12)
      - Bates, Dean Henry M. (Box 11)
        (11-13)
      - Bb-Bi (Box 11)
        (11-14)
      - Bishop, William W. (Box 11)
        (11-15)
      - Bj-Bq (Box 11)
        (11-16)
      - Blakeman, Edvard W. (Box 11)
        (11-17)
      - Board in Control of Athletics (Box 11)
        (11-18)
      - Br-Bz (Box 11)
        (11-19)
      - Bursley, Dean J.A. (Box 11)
        (11-20)
      - Ca-Ch (Box 11)
        (11-21)
      - Ci-Cl (Box 11)
        (11-22)
      - Clements Library (Box 11)
        (11-23)
      - Cm-Co (Box 11)
        (11-24)
      - Cp-Cz (Box 11)
        (11-25)
      - Da-De (Box 11)
        (11-26)
      - Df-Dz (Box 11)
        (11-27)
      - Ea-Ez (Box 11)
        (11-28)
      - Earhart, Harry B. (Box 11)
        (11-29)
      - Edmonson, Dean J.B. (Box 11)
        (11-30)
      - Fa-Fi (Box 12)
        (12-1)
      - F.E.R.A.-C.W.A. (Box 12)
        (12-2)
      - Fj-Fz (Box 12)
        (12-3)
      - Fresh Air Camp (Box 12)
        (12-4)
      - Ga-Gn (Box 12)
        (12-5)
      - Go-Gz (Box 12)
        (12-6)
      - Graduate School (Box 12)
        (12-7)
      - Griffin, Dean C.E. (Box 12)
        (12-8)
      - Gram, L.M. (Box 12)
        (12-9)
      - Ha-Hd (Box 12)
        (12-10)
      - Haynes, Dr. Harley A (Box 12)
        (12-11)
      - He-Hi (Box 12)
        (12-12)
      - Henderson, W.D. (Box 12)
        (12-13)
      - Henderson-Senate Committee (Box 12)
        (12-14)
      - Hj-Hz (Box 12)
        (12-15)
      - I (Box 12)
        (12-16)
      - J (Box 12)
        (12-17)
      - Ka-Kk (Box 12)
        (12-18)
      - Kl-Kz (Box 12)
        (12-19)
      - La-Le (Box 12)
        (12-20)
      - Lawyers Club (Box 12)
        (12-21)
      - Legislature (U.S.) (Box 12)
        (12-22)
      - Lf-Lz (Box 12)
        (12-23)
      - Ma-Mb (Box 12)
        (12-24)
      - Maurer, Wesley H. (Box 12)
        (12-25)
      - Me-Md (Box 12)
        (12-26)
      - Me-Mi (Box 12)
        (12-27)
      - Mj-Mt (Box 12)
        (12-28)
      - Mu-Mz (Box 12)
        (12-29)
      - Na-Nn (Box 13)
        (13-1)
      - National Research Council Conservation (Box 13)
        (13-2)
      - No-Nz (Box 13)
        (13-3)
      - O (Box 13)
        (13-4)
      - Pa-Pe (Box 13)
        (13-5)
      - Pf-Pz (Box 13)
        (13-6)
      - Q (Box 13)
        (13-7)
      - Ra-Re (Box 13)
        (13-8)
      - Rf-Ri (Box 13)
        (13-9)
      - Rj-Ro (Box 13)
        (13-10)
      - R.O.T.C. (Box 13)
        (13-11)
      - Rp-Rz (Box 13)
        (13-12)
      - Sa-Sd (Box 13)
        (13-13)
      - Se-Sj (Box 13)
        (13-14)
      - Sink, Charles A. (Box 13)
        (13-15)
      - Sk-Sp (Box 13)
        (13-16)
      - Scholarships (Box 13)
        (13-17)
      - Shields, Edmund C. (Box 13)
        (13-18)
      - Smith, Ira M. (Box 13)
        (13-19)
      - Smith, Shirley W. (Box 13)
        (13-20)
      - Sq-Sz (Box 13)
        (13-21)
      - Stone, Ralph (Box 13)
        (13-22)
      - T-U (Box 13)
        (13-23)
      - V (Box 13)
        (13-24)
      - Wa-Wh (Box 13)
        (13-25)
      - Wi-Wz (Box 13)
        (13-26)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 13)
        (13-27)
    - 1935-1936
      - Aa-Am (Box 13)
        (13-28)
      - Alumni Association (Box 13)
        (13-29)
      - Alumni Relations (Box 13)
        (13-30)
      - American (Box 13)
        (13-31)
      - An-Az (Box 14)
        (14-1)
      - Anonymous-Asylum (Box 14)
        (14-2)
      - Associations (Box 14)
        (14-3)
      - Ba (Box 14)
        (14-4)
      - Baccalaureate (Box 14)
        (14-5)
      - Bb-Bi (Box 14)
        (14-6)
      - Bishop, William W. (Box 14)
        (14-7)
      - Blakeman, Edward W. (Box 14)
        (14-8)
      - Bl-Br (Box 14)
        (14-9)
      - Bs-Bz (Box 14)
        (14-10)
      - Board in Control of Athletics (Box 14)
        (14-11)
      - Burke, George J. (Box 14)
        (14-12)
      - Ca-Ck (Box 14)
        (14-13)
      - Carr, Lowell (Box 14)
        (14-14)
      - Cl-Co (Box 14)
        (14-15)
      - Clements Library (Box 14)
        (14-16)
      - Cp-Cz (Box 14)
        (14-17)
      - Da-De (Box 14)
        (14-18)
      - Df-Dz (Box 14)
        (14-19)
      - Ea-Eg (Box 14)
        (14-20)
      - Edmonson, J.B. (Box 14)
        (14-21)
      - Eh-Ez (Box 14)
        (14-22)
      - Elliott, Eugene B. (Box 14)
        (14-23)
      - Fa-Fh (Box 14)
        (14-24)
      - F.E.R.A. (Box 14)
        (14-25)
      - Fi-Fq (Box 14)
        (14-26)
      - Fr-Fz (Box 14)
        (14-27)
      - Ga-Go (Box 14)
        (14-28)
      - Gp-Gz (Box 14)
        (14-29)
      - Ha-Rd (Box 14)
        (14-30)
      - He (Box 15)
        (15-1)
      - Henderson, William D. (Box 15)
        (15-2)
      - Hf-Hz (Box 15)
        (15-3)
      - I (Box 15)
        (15-4)
      - Institute for Human Adjustment, 1935-1938 (Box 15)
        (1984 accession; donor no. 6160)
        (15-4a)
      - J (Box 15)
        (15-5)
      - Ka-Kk (Box 15)
        (15-6)
      - Kl-Kz (Box 15)
        (15-7)
      - La-Lb (Box 15)
        (15-8)
      - Lawyers Club (Box 15)
        (15-9)
      - Lc-Lh (Box 15)
        (15-10)
      - Legislature (U.S.) (Box 15)
        (15-11)
      - Li-Lz (Box 15)
        (15-12)
      - Ma-Mb (Box 15)
        (15-13)
      - Me-Mh (Box 15)
        (15-14)
      - Mi (Box 15)
        (15-15)
      - Mj-Mz (Box 15)
        (15-16)
      - N (Box 15)
        (15-17)
      - O (Box 15)
        (15-18)
      - Pa-Pe (Box 15)
        (15-19)
      - Pf-Pz (Box 15)
        (15-20)
      - Questionnaires (Box 15)
        (15-21)
      - Ra-Ri (Box 15)
        (15-22)
      - Rj-Rz (Box 15)
        (15-23)
      - R.O.T.C. (Box 15)
        (15-24)
      - Sa-Sd (Box 15)
        (15-25)
      - Scholarships (Box 15)
        (15-26)
      - Se-Si (Box 15)
        (15-27)
      - Sj-Sp (Box 15)
        (15-28)
      - Smith, Ira M. (Box 15)
        (15-29)
      - Smith, Richard R. (Box 15)
        (15-30)
      - Smith, Shirley W. (Box 15)
        (15-31)
      - Sq-Sz (Box 15)
        (15-32)
      - Stone, Ralph (Box 15)
        (15-33)
      - T (Box 16)
        (16-1)
      - U-V (Box 16)
        (16-2)
      - Wa-Wh (Box 16)
        (16-3)
      - Wi-Wz (Box 16)
        (16-4)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 16)
        (16-5)
    - 1936-1937
      - Aa-Am (Box 16)
        (16-6)
      - Alumni Association (Box 16)
        (16-7)
      - Alumni Relations (Box 16)
        (16-8)
      - American (Box 16)
        (16-9)
      - An-Ar (Box 16)
        (16-10)
      - Anonymous-Asylum (Box 16)
        (16-11)
      - Applications (Box 16)
        (16-12)
      - As-Az (Box 16)
        (16-13)
      - Associations (Box 16)
        (16-14)
      - Ba-Bd (Box 16)
        (16-15)
      - Be-Bk (Box 16)
        (16-16)
      - Bishop, William W. (Box 16)
        (16-17)
      - Bl-Bq (Box 16)
        (16-18)
      - Blakeman, Edward W. (Box 16)
        (16-19)
      - Br-Bz (Box 16)
        (16-20)
      - Bursley, Dean J.A. (Box 16)
        (16-21)
      - Ca-Ce (Box 16)
        (16-22)
      - Centennial (Box 16)
        (16-23)
      - Cf-Co (Box 16)
        (16-24)
      - Clements Library (Box 16)
        (16-25)
      - Cp-Cz (Box 16)
        (16-26)
      - Da-Di (Box 16)
        (16-27)
      - Dj-Dz (Box 16)
        (16-28)
      - Ea-Ez (Box 16)
        (16-29)
      - Earhart, Harry B. (Box 16)
        (16-30)
      - Edmonson, J.B. (Box 16)
        (16-31)
      - Elliott, Eugene B. (Box 16)
        (16-32)
      - Fa-Fq (Box 16)
        (16-33)
      - Football (Box 16)
        (16-34)
      - Fr-Fz (Box 16)
        (16-35)
      - Fraternities (Box 16)
        (16-36)
      - Ga-Gh (Box 17)
        (17-1)
      - Gi-Gn (Box 17)
        (17-2)
      - Go-Gz (Box 17)
        (17-3)
      - Gram, L.M. (Box 17)
        (17-4)
      - Griffin, Clare E. (Box 17)
        (17-5)
      - Ha (Box 17)
        (17-6)
      - Hb-He (Box 17)
        (17-7)
      - Hf-Ho (Box 17)
        (17-8)
      - House and Senate Club (Box 17)
        (17-9)
      - Hp-Hz (Box 17)
        (17-10)
      - I (Box 17)
        (17-11)
      - J (Box 17)
        (17-12)
      - Ka-Kk (Box 17)
        (17-13)
      - Kl-Kz (Box 17)
        (17-14)
      - La-Lh (Box 17)
        (17-15)
      - Lawyers Club (Box 17)
        (17-16)
      - Li-Lz (Box 17)
        (17-17)
      - Ma-Mb (Box 17)
        (17-18)
      - Me-Md (Box 17)
        (17-19)
      - Me-Mh (Box 17)
        (17-20)
      - Mi (Box 17)
        (17-21)
      - Michigan (Box 17)
        (17-22)
      - Mj-Mz (Box 17)
        (17-23)
      - Mosher-Jordan Halls (Box 17)
        (17-24)
      - Murfin, James O. (Box 17)
        (17-25)
      - Murphy, Frank (Box 17)
        (17-26)
      - Na-Ne (Box 17)
        (17-27)
      - National Youth Administration (Box 17)
        (17-28)
      - Near East Research (Box 17)
        (17-29)
      - Nf-Nz (Box 17)
        (17-30)
      - O (Box 17)
        (17-31)
      - Pa-Pe (Box 17)
        (17-32)
      - Pf-Pz (Box 17)
        (17-33)
      - Q (Box 17)
        (17-34)
      - Questionnaires (Box 17)
        (17-35)
      - Ra-Re (Box 17)
        (17-36)
      - Relics, Pins, Seals, Etc. (Box 17)
        (17-37)
      - Rf-Ro (Box 17)
        (17-38)
      - R.O.T.C. (Box 17)
        (17-39)
      - Rp-Rz (Box 17)
        (17-40)
      - Sa-Sb (Box 18)
        (18-1)
      - Sc (Box 18)
        (18-2)
      - Scholarships and Prizes (Box 18)
        (18-3)
      - Schmidt, Julius (Box 18)
        (18-4)
      - Sd-Sh (Box 18)
        (18-5)
      - Si-Sn (Box 18)
        (18-6)
      - Smith, Ira M. (Box 18)
        (18-7)
      - Smith, Richard R. (Box 18)
        (18-8)
      - Smith, Shirley W. (Box 18)
        (18-9)
      - So-St (Box 18)
        (18-10)
      - Stason, E. Blythe (Box 18)
        (18-11)
      - State University Association (Box 18)
        (18-12)
      - Stone, Ralph (Box 18)
        (18-13)
      - Su-Sz (Box 18)
        (18-14)
      - T (Box 18)
        (18-15)
      - U-V (Box 18)
        (18-16)
      - Wa-We (Box 18)
        (18-17)
      - Waggoner, Dr. Raymond (Box 18)
        (18-18)
      - Wf-Wz (Box 18)
        (18-19)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 18)
        (18-20)
    - 1937-1938
      - Aa-Am (Box 18)
        (18-21)
      - Alumni Association (Box 18)
        (18-22)
      - Alumni Relations (Box 18)
        (18-23)
      - American (Box 18)
        (18-24)
      - An-Az (Box 18)
        (18-25)
      - Anonymous-Asylum (Box 18)
        (18-26)
      - Applications for Positions (Box 18)
        (18-27)
      - Associations, Bureaus, etc. (Box 18)
        (18-28)
      - Ba (Box 18)
        (18-29)
      - Bb-Bn (Box 18)
        (18-30)
      - Bishop, William Warner (Box 18)
        (18-31)
      - Blakeman, Edward W. (Box 18)
        (18-32)
      - Bo-Br (Box 18)
        (18-33)
      - Board in Control of Physical Education (Box 18)
        (18-34)
      - Bruce, Dr. James D. (Box 18)
        (18-35)
      - Bs-Bz (Box 18)
        (18-36)
      - Ca-Ce (Box 19)
        (19-1)
      - Carr, Lowell J. (Box 19)
        (19-2)
      - Carrothers, George E. (Box 19)
        (19-3)
      - Ch-Ck (Box 19)
        (19-4)
      - Chicago Club Project (Box 19)
        (19-5)
      - Cl-Cn (Box 19)
        (19-6)
      - Clements Library (Box 19)
        (19-7)
      - Co (Box 19)
        (19-8)
      - Cp-Cz (Box 19)
        (19-9)
      - Da-De (Box 19)
        (19-10)
      - Df-Dz (Box 19)
        (19-11)
      - Ea-Eg (Box 19)
        (19-12)
      - Edmonson, James B. (Box 19)
        (19-13)
      - Educational Policies Commission (Box 19)
        (19-14)
      - Eh-Ez (Box 19)
        (19-15)
      - Elliott, Eugene B. (Box 19)
        (19-16)
      - Fa-Fq (Box 19)
        (19-17)
      - Fr-Fz (Box 19)
        (19-18)
      - Fraternities (Box 19)
        (19-19)
      - Fresh Air Camp (Box 19)
        (19-20)
      - Ga-Gn (Box 19)
        (19-21)
      - Go-Gz (Box 19)
        (19-22)
      - Gram, L.M. (Box 19)
        (19-23)
      - Griffin, Clare E. (Box 19)
        (19-24)
      - Ha (Box 19)
        (19-25)
      - Hb-Hi (Box 19)
        (19-26)
      - Hj-Hz (Box 19)
        (19-27)
      - I (Box 19)
        (19-28)
      - J (Box 19)
        (19-29)
      - Ka-Kh (Box 19)
        (19-30)
      - Ki-Kz (Box 19)
        (19-31)
      - La-Lh (Box 19)
        (19-32)
      - Land Grant Colleges (Box 19)
        (19-33)
      - Law Enforcement (Box 19)
        (19-34)
      - Lawyers Club (Box 19)
        (19-35)
      - Li-Lz (Box 19)
        (19-36)
      - Ma-Mb (Box 19)
        (19-37)
      - Mc-Mh (Box 19)
        (19-38)
      - Mi-Mo (Box 20)
        (20-1)
      - Michigan (Box 20)
        (20-2)
      - Michigan Daily (Box 20)
        (20-3)
      - Mp-Mz (Box 20)
        (20-4)
      - Na-Nz (Box 20)
        (20-5)
      - Nations, etc. (Box 20)
        (20-6)
      - Nelson, J. Raleigh (Box 20)
        (20-7)
      - O (Box 20)
        (20-8)
      - Osborn, Chase S. (Box 20)
        (20-9)
      - Pa-Pn (Box 20)
        (20-10)
      - Po-Pz (Box 20)
        (20-11)
      - Q (Box 20)
        (20-12)
      - Questionnaires (Box 20)
        (20-13)
      - Ra-Ri (Box 20)
        (20-14)
      - Regional Cooperation (Box 20)
        (20-15)
      - Relics, Pins, Seals, etc. (Box 20)
        (20-16)
      - Rj-Rz (Box 20)
        (20-17)
      - Rowe, Kenneth (Box 20)
        (20-18)
      - R.O.T.C. (Box 20)
        (20-19)
      - Ruthven (Box 20)
        (20-20)
      - Sa-Sd (Box 20)
        (20-21)
      - Scholarships, Prizes, etc. (Box 20)
        (20-22)
      - Se-Sn (Box 20)
        (20-23)
      - Shields, Edmund C. (Box 20)
        (20-24)
      - Sink, Charles A. (Box 20)
        (20-25)
      - Smith (Box 20)
        (Miscellaneous)
        (20-26)
      - Smith, Harold D. (Box 20)
        (20-27)
      - Smith, Ira M. (Box 20)
        (20-28)
      - Smith, Richard R. (Box 20)
        (20-29)
      - Smith, Shirley W. (Box 20)
        (20-30)
      - So-Sz (Box 20)
        (20-31)
      - Stason, E. Blythe (Box 20)
        (20-32)
      - Stone, Ralph (Box 20)
        (20-33)
      - Student Religious Association (Box 20)
        (20-34)
      - T (Box 21)
        (21-1)
      - U (Box 21)
        (21-2)
      - V (Box 21)
        (21-3)
      - Wa-Wg (Box 21)
        (21-4)
      - Wallace, Mary Blair (Box 21)
        (21-5)
      - Wh-Wz (Box 21)
        (21-6)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 21)
        (21-7)
    - 1938-1939
      - Aa-Am (Box 21)
        (21-8)
      - Acknowledgments (Box 21)
        (21-9)
      - Advertising (Box 21)
        (21-10)
      - Alumni Association (Box 21)
        (21-11)
      - Alumni Relations (Box 21)
        (21-12)
      - American (Box 21)
        (21-13)
      - American Council on Education (Box 21)
        (21-14)
      - An-Az (Box 21)
        (21-15)
      - Anonymous-Asylum (Box 21)
        (21-16)
      - Applications for Positions (Box 21)
        (21-17)
      - Associations, Bureaus, etc. (Box 21)
        (21-18)
      - Association of American Universities (Box 21)
        (21-19)
      - Ba-Be (Box 21)
        (21-20)
      - Bates, Henry M. (Box 21)
        (21-21)
      - Bf-Bq (Box 21)
        (21-22)
      - Birthday (U.M. Radio) (Box 21)
        (21-23)
      - Bishop, William W. (Box 21)
        (21-24)
      - Blakeman, Edward W. (Box 21)
        (21-25)
      - Br (Box 21)
        (21-26)
      - Bs-Bz (Box 21)
        (21-27)
      - Ca-Cd (Box 21)
        (21-28)
      - Ce-Cn (Box 21)
        (21-29)
      - Clements Library (Box 21)
        (21-30)
      - Co (Box 21)
        (21-31)
      - Cooley Foundation (Box 21)
        (21-32)
      - Cp-Cz (Box 22)
        (22-1)
      - Da-De (Box 22)
        (22-2)
      - Deans (Box 22)
        (22-3)
      - Df-Dz (Box 22)
        (22-4)
      - Dormitories (Box 22)
        (22-5)
      - Ea-Ez (Box 22)
        (22-6)
      - Edmonson, James B. (Box 22)
        (22-7)
      - Educational Policies Committee (Box 22)
        (22-8)
      - Elliott, Eugene B. (Box 22)
        (22-9)
      - Extension Service (Box 22)
        (22-10)
      - Fa-Fk (Box 22)
        (22-11)
      - Fl-Fq (Box 22)
        (22-12)
      - Football (Box 22)